原創翻譯  雙語字幕
最新連載海外影視劇下載
請登陸 www.YYeTs.com
僅供交流學習  禁止商用盈利
翻譯     菜菜  斗斗  Alex  Elena777  大K  Santolalla
翻譯     紅樓采薇 發現一個葚 杏仁斯嘉麗 秋明月
翻譯     Ievo今生后宮已滿  Bobby來世再撩通寶
校對     今生秋明月  來世兔牙貓
時間軸    紙袋P  姜姜  小啾  孫了個大圣  壬虛浪影
后期     8T
總監     somehacker   兔牙Bobby貓
哈勃博士  開始直播之前
Dr. Harber, before we're live,
我只想說  感謝你挑選了我
I just wanted to say thank you for choosing me.
吃葡萄不吐葡萄皮兒
Peter Piper picked a peck of pickled peppers.
你跟其他記者之間有不少嫌隙...
The rich history you have with other journalists...
我特地選了你  就因為我們過往沒有恩怨
I chose you precisely because we don't have a history.
所以別搞砸了
Now, don't fuck it up.
15秒倒計時開始
Fifteen seconds.
人們很信任你  幾十年來  一直很重視你
People trust you... for decades have valued you.
我覺得那是因為人們重視真相
I think that's because people value the truth.
好吧  但你不覺得你將這個「發現」...
Right, but don't you think your discovery was just...
分享給世人是一件很危險的事嗎
too dangerous to share with the world?
聽著  這是我投入了四十年心血研究出的成果
Look, this has been my life's work for over 40 years.
不是隨便得出的結論
There's nothing willy-nilly here.
經過一系列的探討與爭論
After much discussion, much debate,
我們都得出了同樣的結論
we all came to the same conclusion.
-結論是  -就是人們探索完全部的科學可能性之后
- Which is? - Which is, once you explore all scientific possibilities,
大家達成了共識
and you come to a consensus,
這項重大發現攸關人類生死存亡
how can you keep a discovery so vital
怎可不公諸于世
to our existence a secret?
而這個「發現」就是...
And that discovery...
你證明了「來世」的存在
You proved the existence of an afterlife.
我更愿意稱之為「另一個次元世界」
I prefer to call it a new plane of existence.
我不會用「靈魂」  「天堂」  「來世」這種詞來解釋
I can't comment on terminology like "Soul" and "Heaven" and "Afterlife,"
但我可以說  科學證實了
but what I can say with scientific certainty is
身體死亡之后
that once the body dies,
我們的一部分潛意識就會脫離身體
some part of our consciousness leaves us
進入「另一個次元世界」
and travels to a new plane.
你發明的機器能夠捕捉到人死后
Your machine was able to capture brain wavelengths
離開人體的次原子層次腦電波
on a subatomic level, leaving the body after death.
-是這樣...  -沒錯
- Is that...? - That's correct.
那這些腦電波都去了哪里呢
Where do those wavelengths go?
我的重點是  確實存在「另一個次元世界」
My point is, a new plane of existence is out there.
這已無可爭議
Yes, that is no longer in dispute.
但你也無法告訴我們具體是什么
But you can't tell us what that is exactly.
你看到一輛火車離站時
When you see a train leave the station...
你需要通過了解車行駛的目的地
do you need to know where it's going to
而知道車要離開了嗎
understand that you saw it leave?
這種解釋讓人難以接受
It's a tough pill to swallow.
人們以前還不愿接受地球是圓的呢
At one point, so was the Earth being round.
但是  哈勃博士
But, Dr. Harber,
你為何等了六個月才向世人公布
why did it take you six months to address us?
你之前都去哪了
Where have you been?
好像是我邀請你到我家來的吧
It seems to me that I invited you here, to my home.
是  沒錯  謝謝你
Yes, you did. Thank you.
但自殺人數劇增到百萬人之后
But... we only received that invitation
你才邀請我們過來
after the suicide toll had rapidly reached a million.
而在此期間  很多名人  運動員
And during that time, celebrities, athletes,
甚至包括一個你關系親密的同事
even a close colleague of yours,
都結束了自己的生命
all ended their lives.
所以我才同意跟你接受訪問
Which is why I agreed to sit with you
試圖讓人們冷靜下來
and try to calm the waters.
好吧
Okay.
我想問你一個問題
I wanna ask you the question
估計電視機前的觀眾都很想知道
that everybody watching right now is probably wondering.
你覺得這么多人自殺是你的責任嗎
Do you feel responsible for all those people killing themselves?
不是
No.
-就這樣嗎  -就這樣
- That's it? - That's it.
謝謝你  哈勃博士  讓我可以去「來世」重生
Thank you, Dr. Harber... for my fresh start.
安迪  不要
Andy, no!
安迪
Andy!
-安迪  -不
- Andy! - No.
天吶
God!
-你為什么想不開啊  -快叫救護車
- Why would you do that? - Somebody call 911.
快來幫忙
Help! Some....
叫救護車
Call help, please.
趕緊去  叫人來
Right now. Get someone here.
天吶
My God!
你為什么要這么做
Why would you do that?
天吶
God.
關掉攝像機
Turn those cameras off.
發現
歡迎繼續收看 「重大發現」兩周年紀念特輯
Welcome back to our coverage of the two-year anniversary of the Discovery.
我們要重溫過去兩年間的「試金石時刻」
We'll be revisiting the touchstone moments of the past two years,
我們將用一周時間來回顧
with retrospectives all weekend long.
托馬斯·哈勃公布「重大發現」之后
Hard to believe that it's been a year and a half
首次接受了獨家專訪時  有人在節目中自殺
since Thomas Harber's first and only post-Discovery interview
此事竟然已經過去一年半了
ended suddenly with an on-air suicide.
自此之后  全世界的自殺人數
Since then, the worldwide suicide toll
暴增到了令人驚愕的程度
has skyrocketed to staggering levels.
超過四百萬人已經選擇了自殺
Over four million people have taken their lives,
想去往「來世」
attempting to "Get there."
而托馬斯·哈勃博士  自從那次不堪回首的訪談之后
As for Dr. Thomas Harber, he has not made a public appearance
他就再也沒有公開露面
since that infamous post-Discovery interview.
完全隱居了
Completely off the grid--
我正聽著呢
I was listening to that.
抱歉  我以為船上就我一個人
I'm sorry, I thought-- I thought that I was alone.
現在是淡季
It's off-season.
你去這個荒涼的小島干什么
Why the fuck are you going to this dreary island?
你不也去嗎
Well, you're going there.
你是電影院里那種
Are you one of those lunatics who just sits
會跑到一個陌生人旁邊坐下來的神經病嗎
next to a complete stranger in an empty movie theater?
你看起來好眼熟
You look so familiar to me.
我們有可能見過
It's possible we've met,
但你的長相太普通  讓人記不住啊
but you don't have a memorable face.
好吧
Okay.
抱歉  我不知道我怎么說這種話
I'm sorry. I don't know why I said that.
我不是那個意思  我就是...
I didn't mean that. I just...
水的關系  我有點暈船
The water. I'm just a little seasick.
真是怪了  你很走運啊
That's weird. It's your lucky day.
我出門一般不帶著這玩意
I don't normally carry these around.
-頭暈藥  -我不暈
- Vertigo. - I'm not dizzy.
頭暈治不好  藥只是能緩解惡心的癥狀
You can't treat vertigo, just the effects. That's for nausea.
我看起來像是那種
Do I look like the kind of girl
隨便接受陌生人藥物的女孩嗎
who's just gonna take a pill from some strange guy?
說得倒也是
Fair enough.
艾拉  我叫艾拉
Isla. My name's Isla.
愛爾蘭語  名字意為「島嶼」
盡管我看起來不像「艾拉」
I don't look like an Isla, though.
三歲之前
Your first three years,
人的長相和名字都很搭
you look like whatever name you're given,
到了4歲  你要么變得人如其名要么就...
then by four, you either settle into your name or you just...
-你呢  -什么
- What about you? - What?
你叫什么
What's your name?
威爾·史蒂文森
Will Stevenson.
威爾
Will.
怎么了
What?
我就是在想你的長相跟名字搭不搭
I'm just trying to see if you look like your name.
-你的結論是  -說不好
- What's the verdict there? - I don't know.
現在還言之過早
It's too early to tell.
「威爾」是個很隨意的名字
You know, Will is just such a, like, "Will" Name.
你真挺與眾不同啊
You're really something.
「重大發現」兩周年快樂  威爾
Happy second Discovery anniversary, Will.
自殺不是良策
堅守此生
#別再自殺了  #發現生活
新聞上說據預測
They said on the news
今天又會有大批人自殺
they're expecting like a whole slew of suicides today.
大家想去「來世」慶祝周年紀念
People trying to get there for the anniversary.
這我也聽說了
I heard something about that.
你看過那個視頻嗎  就一群白癡拉拉隊員
Did you see that video of those dumb cheerleaders
在球場上吞藥的那個
taking pills on the 50-yard line?
我真無法理解這種自殺組織的概念
I just can't get behind the concept of suicide groups.
這太虛偽了
It's so... disingenuous, you know?
我就是感覺太軟弱了
It just feels so weak.
你不相信「重大發現」嗎
You don't believe in the Discovery?
不  我不信的是自殺組織
No, I don't believe in suicide groups.
「重大發現」是  事實勝于雄辯
The Discovery is-- I mean, the proof is overwhelming.
「事實勝于雄辯」還不夠  要拿出確鑿證據
Proof shouldn't be overwhelming. Proof should be definitive.
所以你并不信
So, you don't believe.
我是不相信別人信的那一套
I don't believe the way everybody else does.
對  我不信
No, I don't.
-此話怎講  -我是個神經科醫生
- And how's that? - I'm a neurologist.
三個月前  我診治了一個病人  她很年輕
Three months ago, I had a patient, really young,
診斷下來她有腦癌  我很遺憾
found out that she had brain cancer. Very sad.
而她對此卻表現得
She reacted to that diagnosis
像是我遞給了她一張中了獎的彩票
as though I'd handed her a fucking winning lottery ticket.
并不是因為她希望
It wasn't because she hoped
或許她死后能上天堂
that maybe she was going someplace better.
而是因為「重大發現」
It was because the Discovery
讓她堅信一定會去更好的地方
made her think that it was guaranteed.
是啊  我們以前對待死亡只能聽天由命
Well, yeah. Death used to be something we just had to live with,
而如今死亡只是逃避痛苦的便捷手段
and now it's a convenient way to escape pain.
-這沒什么  -沒什么
- That's okay. - That's okay?
「另一個次元世界」  大概存在吧
Another plane of existence, maybe.
誰知道呢
Who knows?
但我環顧四周
But I look around,
只看見一幫人跳下飛機
I see a lot of people jumping out of planes
希望自己會長出翅膀
hoping they're gonna grow wings.
現實和幻想是相斥的
Reality and fantasy are mutually exclusive.
他們是無法共存的
They don't exist in the same space.
你想說什么
What?
我5歲的時候  出過一次事故
When I was five, I had an accident,
「死」了一分鐘左右
and I died for about a minute.
我被救醒后 我跟父母說我看見了一些東西
When I was resuscitated, I told my parents that I saw something.
閃光  一個小男孩
Flashes. A little boy.
可能是我  或者我弟弟
Me, maybe, or my brother.
我感覺被困住了
I felt stranded...
困在哪兒了
Stranded where?
空蕩的海灘  這不重要  那只是個夢
This empty beach. It doesn't matter. It was a dream.
是個我醒來后  自己添油加醋過的夢
It was a dream that I embellished after I woke up.
你為什么要編這個故事出來
Why would you make all that up?
我覺得追尋意義是我們的本能
I think it's our instinct to search for meaning,
而一旦遍尋不著  我們就會本能地制造意義
and when there is none, it's our instinct to create meaning
我們會直接撒謊  自欺欺人
and we just... lie. We lie to ourselves.
你真煩人啊  有人這么對你說過嗎
You are so annoying. Has anyone ever told you that?
嗯  有的
Yeah, they have.
還好再等一分鐘我搭上車后
Thank God we only have a minute left together
我們就分道揚鑣了
before we're strangers again.
你覺得這個時節等一分鐘就能等到嗎  你瘋了啊
You think it's gonna be a minute this time of year? You're crazy.
是瘋  但我沒說錯
Crazy, but right.
你是個美女  我沒把這點計算在內
That's the attractive-girl component and I didn't factor that in.
你的數學有待提高啊
You'd better work on your math.
不管怎樣  我覺得你確實很像「艾拉」
For whatever it's worth, I think you do look like an Isla.
你見過多少個「艾拉」
How many of us have you met?
-我來吧  -不  我來  兄弟
- I got it. - No, I got it, man.
我可不想死在半路上  托比
Well, I don't want to die before we get there, Toby.
-這里發生什么了  -埃迪
- What's going on over here? - Eddie.
等下  埃迪·埃厄戴斯  埃迪死了
Wait, Eddie Iodice? Eddie died?
嗯  就為了去往「來世」
Yeah, just to get there.
去往該死的「來世」
Just to fucking get there.
他學瑪麗蓮·夢露
Guy pulled a Marilyn Monroe,
在臥室里吞了一整瓶藥
downed a whole bottle of pills right there in his bedroom.
那哥們人挺好的
Good dude, too.
-真的很遺憾  -你不想去參加葬禮嗎
- Real pity. - You didn't wanna go to the service?
去參加
Go to the...?
我寧愿把小雞雞插木材切片機里
I would rather stick my dick in a wood chipper
-也不想再參加一場該死的葬禮了  -懂了
- than go to another fucking funeral. - Got it.
我沒有你想象中那么傻
You know, I'm not as stupid as you might think.
那天你打電話來  我對你說
When you called the other day and I told you
爸又造了個新玩意兒...
that Dad had built something new...
那次通話后
after that conversation...
你突然就想回家了
suddenly you wanted to come home.
你這話說得像是跟他一樣多疑
You're sounding just as paranoid as him.
爸說他得換個地方
Dad said he needed to change things up.
暴露我們的地址太危險了
People knowing our address was too dangerous.
我很抱歉我不能在電話里告訴你
I'm sorry I couldn't tell you on the phone,
我們現在已經不信任電話了
but we don't trust phones now.
我們到了
Here we are.
去見「大魔法師」吧
Off to see the wizard.
這是什么鬼地方
What the fuck is this place?
這里本來是「問題少年」的夏令營營地
It used to be a summer camp for "Troubled youths."
我一直不明白
Which I never really understood,
如果他們都是壞孩子了
because if they're bad kids,
哪還有資格過有趣的暑假呢  你說呢
why would they deserve a fun summer? You know?
后來夏令營關了  被爸買下了
But then it shut down and Dad bought it.
你覺得如何
What do you think?
我覺得這簡直荒唐至極
I think it's completely insane.
事實上
Well, the truth is
我們需要更多收容空間
we just needed a lot more space to house things.
收容什么
House what things?
這些人都受到「重大發現」的影響
These people were all affected by the Discovery.
他們中有些人
Some of them arrived here
經過兩三次自殺未遂后來到這里
after two or three failed suicide attempts.
我們為其提供住所
We gave them a home,
提供活下去的動力  積極貢獻的理由
something to live for in this life, a reason to contribute.
有點小事
Real quick.
提醒下  類似聯邦局標準  禁止攜帶手機
Just FYI, FBI-type thing, protocol is no cell phones.
-好  行  我們走吧  -好
- Yeah, okay. Let's go. - Yeah.
別擔心
Hey, don't worry.
這真令人興奮
This is truly thrilling.
唯一能與其媲美的就是
I can only compare it to the model train set
我生日時  你讓我自己組裝的火車模型
you let me assemble by myself on my birthday.
時間有點太緊了
Cutting it a little close.
你了解我
Well, you know me.
坐如針氈  緊張不安
Pins and needles, needles and pins.
這些破爛機器
These goddamn machines.
-他是誰  -他的另一個兒子剛回來了
- Who the hell's that? - His other son just returned.
沒想到比我想象中要高一些
Surprisingly taller than I remember.
很高興我們又見面了  庫珀
Good to see you again, Cooper.
威爾  這是萊西  萊西...
Will, Lacey. Lacey...
「挺順利的開場」
That went well.
老爸在哪
Where's Dad?
-他死了嗎  -沒  當然沒有
- Is he dead? - No, of course not.
他現在死了
He is now.
-15秒  -老爸
- Fifteen seconds. - Dad?
別激動  他們只是做些測試而已
Take it easy. They're just running some tests.
-都是些常規試驗  -10秒
- It's all routine. - Ten seconds.
除顫儀已充電...  準備就緒
Paddles charged... and ready.
他們通過電擊身體來重啟大腦
See, they're recharging the body to reboot the brain.
他最長一次試驗記錄  大概有60秒
The longest he's ever officially under is, like, 60 seconds.
這么說  老爸是先自殺  然后再被電活
So, Dad is now killing himself and electroshocking back to life.
不是
No.
差不多
Kind of.
但是你...  不是你想象中那樣
But you're... You're looking at this all wrong.
你總站在那個什么的對立面...
You're wearing whatever the opposite of...
什么來著  樂觀態度
What is it? Rose-colored glasses.
你就是那種態度
That's what you're wearing.
太悲觀
Shit-colored glasses.
總之  你不用擔心
Anyway, you shouldn't worry,
因為一切都受到嚴密監視  都在掌控之內
because all of this is being closely monitored and controlled.
而且我們都知道
And we both know
你對什么事都抱著懷疑的態度
you've always been slightly skeptical of everything.
老爸成立了個邪教
Dad started a cult.
-沒有  -你看不出來嗎  這就是個邪教
- No. - Can you not see that? This is a cult.
到處都是穿著不同顏色連體褲的信徒
All the way down to these followers in different-colored jumpsuits.
不  不  這里沒有階級  威爾
No, no, no. There's no hierarchy here, Will.
老爸管這叫做...  許可級別差異
Dad calls it... distinctions in clearance.
只是這樣  這不是邪教
That's all. It's not a cult.
應該換個「約束服」
It should be different. Straitjackets.
不管出于什么原因
You're the one that wanted to come back here
是你自己主動回來的  記得吧
if you remember for whatever reason. Right?
這個就是最有價值的問題了
Now, that, right there, is the million-dollar question.
歡迎回來  威爾
Welcome back, Will.
你有什么想對我說的嗎
You mind telling me something?
你回來有什么事
What are you doing back here?
我回來是想讓你叫停這一切
I'm here because I want you to stop it.
我想讓你結束這一切
I'm asking you just to put an end to all this.
我要怎么做
How would I do that?
承認你自己錯了
Say that you were wrong.
收回說過的話
Take it all back.
我不能收回  因為這是事實
I can't take it back, Will, because it's the truth.
沒人比你更清楚這點
Who knows better than you?
你可是這一切的靈感來源
You were the inspiration for this.
難道你不好奇嗎
Aren't you curious?
千萬別這么說  那不是...
Please, don't say that. That's not...
-我不是  -但就是你
- I wasn't. - But you were.
等一下
Hang on.
「因此  我相信
"Therefore, it is my belief
意識應該被視為是另一種物質狀態」
consciousness should be considered as another state of matter."
-別念了  -別急
- Please don't. - Hang on.
我還想念下這段  這段寫得更好
I'd like to get to this other part. It gets good.
「意識之屬性始于
"Properties of consciousness arise
支配我們宇宙的物理定律」
from the physical laws that govern our universe."
-我錯了  -你才不信自己錯了
- I was wrong. - You don't believe that.
我們錯了  老爸
We were wrong, Dad.
我們錯了  因為好多人都死了
We were wrong because a lot of people died.
還有更多的人在走上自殺之路...
And a whole lot more people are gonna kill themselves...
而你卻在這座荒謬的城堡里進行實驗
while you experiment here in this ridiculous fortress.
你要就讓我四十年的研究就付之東流嗎
So, just slamming on the brakes of 40 years' work?
那我將難辭其咎
I'd be saying I'm responsible.
或許你確實是
Maybe you are.
所以  你覺得我太過火了嗎
So, you think I've gone too far?
我不覺得我做得還不夠徹底
Well, I don't think I've gone far enough.
我們敞開門接收這些人  威爾
We opened the door for these people, Will.
他們知道「來世」存在
They know it's there.
我們得向他們展示其背后的真面目
Now we have to show them what's behind it.
艾拉
Isla!
該死
Fuck!
-你干什么啊  -你有毛病啊
- What are you doing? - What's your problem?
快  站起來  起來
Come on. Stand up. Get up.
你為什么要這么做
Why are you doing this?
不關你的事
None of your fucking business.
你坐在那艘該死的渡輪上
You sat there on that fucking ferry
和我交談了一番
and had a conversation with me,
其實已經鐵了心要這么做了
knowing you were gonna do this the whole time.
你本該是我生前最后交談的人
You were supposed to be the last person I ever spoke to.
你不能隨便就改變這一切
You don't get to just change that!
你連面對死亡都不帶感情
You're not even emotional about dying.
我對一切都沒有感情
I'm not emotional about anything.
我只是擔心...
I'm just concerned...
有人會曲解這件事
that this will all be perceived unfavorably by some.
她會得肺炎  托比
She was going to catch pneumonia, Toby.
我還是不懂  你想讓我怎么幫她
I still don't know what you want me to do with her.
你告訴我  你們接納需要幫助的人
You told me that you take in people who need help.
她需要幫助
She needs help.
她不能就這樣留下
She still can't just stay here.
我們有規定
We have rules.
那就不能為她破例一次嗎  求你了
Then can we make an exception... in her case, please?
這可關系到一條人命啊
We're talking about somebody's life.
我們都不知道她會不會再企圖...
We have no idea if she will attempt or try to...
再次自殺
Kill myself again?
你明說就好
You can say it.
我清楚事情的始末
I know what happened.
我眼睜睜看著你毀掉了我的自殺計劃
I was there when you ruined it.
她和我相處得很愉快
She and I have been getting along great.
但我們還是有規定
We still have rules.
她得和老爸談談
She has to talk to Dad,
也得完成問卷
and she has to take the questionnaire.
什么問卷
What's the questionnaire?
我們能...
Can we be...?
威爾  你有客人啊
Will, you have a visitor.
你父親是托馬斯·哈勃
Your dad is Thomas Harber?
除了問卷調查員  也就是我
So, nobody but the conductor, which is me,
沒人會知道你的回答
is gonna know your answers.
這里每件事都完全保密
Everything is completely discreet here.
萊西會出去  這里將只有你我二人
And now Lacey will be giving us some privacy.
以前  人們關注全球探索
It used to be about global exploration,
發現新大陸
you know, discovering new land,
后來又將目光轉向太空旅行了
and then it was space travel.
揭開宇宙黑暗一角的真面目
Shining a light on the dark corners of the universe.
如今的關注點在于探索「來世」
And now it's exploring what comes after this life.
探求「來世」的模樣
Seeing what's next.
你多大了
How old are you?
你們都是相同事物的一份子
You are all part of the same thing.
肌體的細胞
Cells in a body.
大海的波浪
Waves in the ocean.
靈魂無關年齡
The soul isn't young or old.
不是我們能夠提高的
It isn't ours to improve.
你認可這一事實嗎
Do you accept the fact that
時間是人為制造的非線性錯覺
time is a nonlinear illusion created by man?
下一題  我不懂這題什么意思
Pass. I don't know what that means.
這份問卷沒有標準答案
There are no right or wrong answers to this questionnaire.
那你為什么要問呢
Then why do you bother giving it?
問得好
That's a good response.
好  請說出你長處及弱點所在
Okay, greatest ability... and most disappointing weakness.
我擅長發現別人的行事意圖
I guess I'm good at seeing what makes somebody tick.
了解他們真實的自我
Understanding who they really are.
弱點呢
Weakness?
我能理解他們
I'm able to understand them,
但無法感同身受
but I'm not able to care about them.
如果有人對你提起了「潛意識」一詞
If somebody mentions "subconscious" to you,
你會想到什么
what do you think?
-記憶  -再往深處想一下
- Memory. - Dig deeper.
潛藏的記憶
Hidden memory.
你會壓抑情感嗎
Would you say that you suppress emotions?
我真的不太喜歡以這種方式談論自己
I don't really like talking about myself like this.
你不必喜歡這種方式
You don't have to like it.
我們每天都在審視自己
We think about ourselves every day.
我們對事物的認知來源于自身的觀點
Everything is from our own perspective.
所以  即使你不愿沉浸于
So, as much as you may not want to indulge yourself
審視內心深處的想法中
in looking at your most inner thoughts,
也無法否認其存在
they're there.
毫無疑問  思想真實存在
Make no mistake. They are there.
你相信靈魂的存在嗎
Do you believe in a soul?
如果不相信  就閉上眼睛
If not, close your eyes.
很好  假設靈魂真實存在
Great. Let's just say a soul does exist.
你覺得會位于身體的哪個部位呢
Where in the body do you think it'd be?
如果靈魂真實存在  應該會大腦中吧
I think if there's a soul, it would belong in the brain.
有點意思
Now, that's interesting.
多數人認為在腸胃中
Most people say the stomach.
但我很欣賞你的回答
But I like that you didn't.
你有過突然失去所愛之人的經歷嗎
Have you ever experienced sudden loss?
有
Yes.
那么  痛失所愛后恢復正常的過程中
And what aspect of regaining normalcy after losing someone...
最艱難的一點是什么
was the most difficult?
大概是冷冰冰的物體吧
Inanimate objects, maybe?
比如...  我的咖啡桌
Like... my coffee table.
陪伴了我很多年
I've had it for years
而且  我大概注視過無數遍了
and I've probably looked at it a million times,
但自從他...
but after he--
熟悉的事物變得扭曲而陌生
Familiar objects just became distorted and unfamiliar.
我開始厭棄我的吊扇  麥片碗  茶壺
I started to hate my ceiling fan, my cereal bowl, my tea kettle.
好  最后一個問題
Okay, last question.
你真有自殺傾向嗎
Are you legitimately suicidal?
如果你知道「來世」的模樣
If you knew what came after... this life...
你覺得那會影響你做出的決定
do you think it would affect your decision-making
亦或甚至使你改變想法嗎
or maybe even make you change your mind?
可能會  已知會改變很多事情
Maybe. Knowing could change things.
你怎么知道自己會住這一間
How'd you know this is where you'd be staying?
我認出了我們以前的床
I found our old bed.
嗯  確實是
Yeah, I see that.
這么說來  你該感謝我
And you should thank me... by the way,
因為我費了好大勁才將這里保持原狀
because I fought long and hard to keep old faithful here.
艾拉怎么樣了
How's Isla?
我正是為這事而來
That's actually why I'm here.
威爾  她死了
Will, she's dead.
不  她沒死  她沒死
No, she's not. She's not dead.
就是說個冷笑話
That was a bad joke.
但問卷已經做完了
But the questionnaire is all wrapped up.
她可以留下
She can stay.
嗯  很好  她需要有人照顧
Yeah, good. She needs to be looked after.
她有可能再次自殺
She could try again.
我覺得那不太可能  威爾
I don't think that's going to happen, Will.
因為今晚...
Because tonight...
一切都將改變
everything changes.
我們終于揭開了「它」的面紗
We finally unveil it.
「它」是什么  托比
What is "It," Toby?
爸希望我邀請你參加今晚一個小集會
Dad wanted me to invite you to a little gathering tonight,
只有被選中的人才能參會
just a select group.
天  我們以前在家可完全不是這樣
Boy, this is nothing like our old house.
在我看來  你很贊同謀殺
It sounds to me a lot like you're advocating murder.
我不贊同謀殺
I'm not advocating murder.
我只是想說
I'm just pointing out that
多數人認為  終結他人的生命
most people don't look at ending somebody else's life
與終結自己的生命有所不同
the way they do their own.
他在哪里
Where is he?
就快要開始了
It's about to happen.
我搞不清你是不是在對我說話
I can't tell when you're talking to me or that.
真讓人惱火
It's really annoying.
總之  我想說的是
Anyways, what I'm saying is,
人們在通過自殺去往「來世」
people are killing themselves to get there.
到某個階段
At a certain point,
他們會用同樣的邏輯殺死別人
they'll use the same logic to kill somebody else,
因為他們只是把「死者」送往別的世界了  是吧
'cause they're just sending them somewhere else, right?
他終于來了
Finally, he's here.
他沒穿我留給他的臨時連體服
And he is not wearing the temp jumpsuit I had left for him.
大腦在處理經歷與體驗時
We're programmed to process our experiences
總是按照開始與結束處理
as having a beginning and an end,
而這在現實中是不存在的
when, in reality... doesn't exist.
存在的只有冗長乏味的中間過程
It's just one long, drawn-out middle.
你們中有些人比其他人來得晚
Some of you are newer than others,
但我想挑選些人成立一個小組
but I wanted to create a select group
來看看我的創造成果
that could see what it is that I built.
但這么做之前  我想花點時間
But before we do that, I'd like to take a moment
請你們和我一起
and have you join me in...
感恩祈禱
bowing our heads...
讓潛意識帶領你們去往他處
And let your subconscious... take you somewhere else.
我有些驚訝  你這么輕易就融入了這里
I'm sort of amazed that you get swept up in this, this easily.
你看起來不是那種動不動就祈禱的人
You don't strike me as a say-your-prayers type.
不信仰上帝
Just because somebody doesn't believe in God
并不意味著不能祈禱
doesn't mean they can't pray.
哪種無神論者會同上帝對話
What kind of an atheist talks to God?
你為什么跟我瞎說了你的姓
Why did you give me a phony, bullshit last name?
不是瞎說  是我母親的娘家姓
It wasn't phony. It was my mother's maiden name.
她人呢
Where is she?
她死了
She's dead.
怎么死的
How did she die?
是因為我父親
Because of my dad.
讓我們回到當下
Let us come back into this moment.
現在我要給大家一個機會
I now offer you the opportunity...
看看「來世」的樣子
to see the afterlife.
我能記錄到我們會去哪里了
I can now record where we go.
請盡快簽完字
Please... get these back to us
把文件還給我們
at your earliest convenience.
再次申明  這些住宿舍是暫時的
And again, these living quarters are just temporary
我們會為你找到更適宜的房間
until we can find you a more suitable room.
我剛搬來的時候  睡在廚房的小床上
When I first moved here, I slept on a cot in the kitchen.
「很豪華」
Glamorous.
我本該沉入海底的
I'm supposed to be at the bottom of the ocean,
所以這樣就很不錯了
so this should be fine.
能借我支筆嗎
Can I have a pen?
保密協議
Nondisclosure agreement.
考慮到敏感性
Well, considering the sensitivity,
這樣的標準性文件很必要
it's a fairly standard document.
你能出去一下嗎
Could we have the room for a second, please?
還記得那糟糕的一周嗎
You remember that awful week
我們睡在冰箱旁的折疊床上
when we slept on the cot by the fridge?
我的背痛得至今記憶猶新
My back sure hasn't forgotten.
我知道那個裝置非常引人入勝
So... I know that that device is very compelling.
我們能聊一下嗎
Can we talk about it for a second?
我不能聊這些
I'm not allowed to talk about it,
因為我剛簽了保密協議
'cause I just signed a nondisclosure agreement.
你父親是有些詭異  可又如何
So, your dad's a little weird. Who cares?
這不代表他說錯了
It doesn't make him wrong.
坡和他表妹上床了
I mean, Poe fucked his cousin.
埃德加·愛倫·坡  美國詩人  浪漫主義思潮時期的重要成員
但這沒影響他在文學界的地位
It didn't make him any less a writer.
我想看看那個機器是不是真像他描述得那么厲害
I wanna see if that machine does what he thinks it does.
如果確實是呢
Well, what if it did?
那會有什么改變呢
How would that change things?
旅游度假前  總要先看宣傳冊吧
You don't go on vacation without looking at the brochure first.
抱歉  你睡了嗎
I'm sorry. Were you sleeping?
我站著呢
I'm standing.
也是
Well, yeah.
但總要這樣問一句吧
That's just something you're supposed to say, I guess.
既然你還沒睡
Since you're up,
能否下樓來  幫我看個東西呢
mind coming downstairs and taking a look at something for me?
當然
Yeah, sure.
我們失去的  其實并未失去...
Those that we have lost are not lost at all...
你們去哪里
Where are you guys going?
沒事  你別操心
It's nothing. Don't worry about it.
其實是我們迷失了
...then it's us who are lost.
當他心跳停止時
When he flatlines,
你可以想象成是關掉了一盞燈
think of it as a light bulb turned off by a switch.
把開關扳上  又扳下
Flip it on, flip it off.
但失去意識  連上新的儀器
But going under, hooked up to the new device,
可就不止是扳動電燈開關了
you're not just flipping a light switch.
基本上等同于拆開整個燈泡
You're essentially detaching the entire bulb.
因此我得說  如果你再次失去意識
So, I'd say that if you go under again...
蘇醒后  將會幾乎失去大腦功能
you're coming back with next to no brain functionality.
我很驚訝這居然還沒發生
I'm sort of surprised it hasn't happened already.
我知道你想第一個嘗試
I know you wanted to be first,
但如果你回不來  這又有什么意義呢
but if you don't come back, what's the point?
我們還是從頭再開始吧
We just go back to the drawing board. Right?
還是能行得通  只是得找個新的辦法...
I mean, it could still work, we just need to find a new way to...
我們需要一具尸體
We need a cadaver.
好吧  抱歉打斷你們
Okay. I'm sorry to interrupt.
你們打算去哪里找尸體
Where do you guys plan on getting a corpse?
我有個辦法
I have a corpse idea.
我很失禮嗎
Am I being rude?
-我很失禮嗎  -不啊
- Am I being rude? -No.
-想聽聽音樂嗎  -好啊
- Care to... listen? - Sure.
寧靜的夜  歡快帶感的節奏
Crunchy groovy grooves. Serene nights.
能問你一件事嗎
Can I ask you something?
威爾之前談起你母親的事
Will mentioned what happened to your mom earlier.
她自殺的事嗎
That she killed herself?
沒這么說
Not exactly.
她是想去「來世」嗎
So, she was trying to get there?
不  那是發生在「重大發現」好多年之前的事了
No, that was a good couple years before the Discovery.
自殺不是良策  堅守此生
進來吧
Yeah.
你好嗎
How you doing?
活著呢  身處亡者之中
In the midst of life, I am in death.
太詭異了
That was weird.
不知道你能不能幫我個忙
I was just wondering if you could help me out.
我的表哥  比利
My, cousin, Billy...
失蹤了
he's gone missing.
剛好是「重大發現」兩周年紀念日
And it being the two-year anniversary of the Discovery,
我們都有點擔心
we're all just a little worried.
很擔心
Really worried.
我們這周收到三具無名男尸
We got three John Does in this week.
他失蹤多久了
How long has he been missing?
不是  不是  比利不在這里
Nope. No. No Billy here.
真糟
Bummer.
如果是  我就能輕松不少了
Would have made my life a hell of a lot easier.
對不起  沒有考慮到你的感受
Sorry, that was insensitive.
只是尸體泛濫成災  我都快瘋了
They just got me running rampant here.
我一個人做著五個人的工作量
I'm doing the job of five people.
淡季裁員之類的  我明白
Off-season cutbacks and whatnot? Yeah.
我能給你描述一下比利長什么樣子嗎
Can I give you a description... of Billy?
這樣如果他真被送到這里
That way if he does... come in,
麻煩幫我留意一下
you can keep an eye out for him.
當然可以
Of course.
去我辦公室說吧
Let's go to my office.
小心地滑
我只是有點好奇
Hey, so, just curious...
我想說的是
I'd like to point out you're
你想在這么多尸體中找到符合條件的目標太難了
reading off a laundry list of corpse requirements.
這位得了腦動脈瘤  不行
Aneurysm, that won't work.
既然我們都已經入室盜竊了
It'd be nice if you could help me,
你就幫幫忙好不好
seeing as we're breaking and entering.
他長得就是一副氣鼓鼓的樣子
Like a real, like, pouty-type face.
還有就是...
And then...
他有塊胎記  長在...
he's got a birthmark on...
我想想  右邊胳膊肘的位置
Let's see. On his right elbow.
我說的特征  你一個都沒記下來
You're not writing any of this down.
我覺得你說得已經很詳細  不用再說了
Well, I think I've got more than I need to go on here, so...
但是我還沒有描述他下半身的特征呢
But we... We haven't even gotten to the lower half of his body.
你不覺得很不可思議嗎
Don't you think it's weird
幾個小時之前這些人還活著
how these people were alive a few hours ago?
他們有恐懼  有欲望  還會焦慮
They had fears and desires, they could exercise?
我不覺得不可思議  我覺得真可悲
I don't think it's weird. I think it's fucking sad.
或許他們去了一個更好的世界呢
Maybe they went someplace better.
或許他們去了一個更差的世界
Maybe they went someplace worse.
或許他們去的地方
Maybe they went someplace that
我們完全不能理解  毫無頭緒
we can't even begin to comprehend.
那就更應該看看你爸的機器能顯示什么
All the more reason to see what your dad's machine shows us.
該死
Shit.
怎么了
What?
「五十二歲  心肌梗死」
"Fifty-two, massive coronary."
威爾
Will...
來認識一下帕特·菲利普斯
meet Pat Phillips.
帕特·菲利普斯  這位是威爾
Pat Phillips, this is Will.
我不喜歡庫珀給我安排的嚇人房間
I don't like that creepy room Cooper put me in.
今晚我就睡你屋里了
I'm gonna sleep in your room tonight.
你睡上鋪還是下鋪
Top or bottom?
我們可以聊聊天
We could talk, you know.
我緊張的時候  要么話很多要么不說話
When I'm nervous, I talk too much or not at all.
這里講話很安全
Well, you're safe here.
上下鋪說過的話  都不會傳出去
I mean... nothing leaves the bunk beds.
我剛來時  他們給了我那件連體服
When I first got here and they gave me that jumpsuit,
上面繡著一個字母「V」
it had a V etched on it.
我想知道那是什么意思
I wonder what that stood for.
可能是「訪客」的意思
"Visitor," Maybe?
你是猜的嗎
Is that a guess?
猜得很有道理
That was a pretty good guess.
就像有的答案很明顯
It's like one of those really obvious answers
但是只有知道答案之后  才會恍悟
that only seems obvious after you find out about it.
你小時候是不是很聰明  你肯定是吧
Were you really smart growing up? I bet you were.
他們說我很早就顯示出
I was told that I demonstrated an early ability
識別空間格局的能力
to recognize spatial patterns,
不知道那是什么意思
whatever that means.
我一直覺得那就是老師對家長的一套說辭
I always took it as one of those things a teacher tells to
他們孩子表現差  這樣說讓他們好受些
a parent to make them feel better about their shitty kid.
比如說「戈登非常擅長畫圓圈
Like, "Gordon is very good at drawing circles.
戈登畫的圓圈
Gordon draws circles at a
比其他孩子畫得都高級」
more advanced level than the other children."
上下鋪真不錯
These bunk beds really worked out well,
一點都不尷尬  不用和你說
'cause they spared me the awkwardness of
我不想跟你上床
having to tell you I'm not gonna fuck you.
不好意思  我只聽到
Sorry, all I heard was
你說什么圓圈  還有不想和我上床
something about circles and not fucking me.
我不想自己一個人在上鋪煩心  威爾
I don't wanna be the only fucked up person on this bunk bed, Will.
要不然  你跟我說說你媽的事吧
Maybe... tell me about your mom now.
沒什么好說的  她自殺了
There's not much to tell. She killed herself.
在結婚紀念日當天自殺的
On their anniversary.
她是怎么自殺的
How did she do it?
她準備了二人晚餐
She made them dinner,
而我爸都沒出辦公室
and... my dad didn't even come out of his office.
如果當時他就是表示一下他還在乎她
If he'd even just hinted that he gave a shit,
誰知道結局會不會不同呢
I mean, who knows?
但是誰都不能打擾他  媽媽就上樓...
But he couldn't be bothered. So, she went upstairs...
去泡澡了
took a bath instead and,
第二天早上  我發現她死在浴缸里
Yeah, the next morning I found her in the tub.
所以你就離家出走了
And so, you left?
是的  沒辦法  我知道沒法留在家里
Yeah, I had to. I couldn't be around it. I knew.
就好像以前熟悉的一切
It's like everything that was recognizable
突然變得陌生起來
sort of instantly became unrecognizable.
有時候我覺得自己占了其他人的位置
Sometimes I feel like I'm taking someone else's spot
我感覺很悲哀
and then I feel sad.
這話什么意思
How do you mean?
就是  浪費生命的感覺
Like, being here alive is a waste
因為我不喜歡活著
because... I don't enjoy it,
我不幸福  也不去感恩
I'm not happy or grateful...
我覺得我活著占了其他人的位置
and I'm taking a spot away from someone who
如果是別人  可能會把人生過得更有意義
maybe would've gotten something more out of it.
好吧
Yeah.
生命的規則應該不是這樣吧
I guess I don't think it works that way.
我從來沒聽別人討論過一個問題
Here's something I haven't heard anyone talk about.
動物有「來世」嗎
Do animals have an afterlife?
兔子  貓咪  小豬  猴子之類的
Bunnies, kittens, pigs, monkeys.
它們死后會怎么樣
What happens to them after they die?
我真心覺得動物們值得擁有「來世」
I mean, I feel like they really deserve an afterlife.
動物有不同于人類的「來世」嗎
Do they have their own animal afterlife?
如果有  是按照物種劃分的嗎
And if they do, is it subdivided by species?
我覺得像「來世」這么意義深刻的事
Because it feels like something as profound as an afterlife
不應該區別對待
shouldn't practice segregation.
孩子們又會怎樣呢
And what happens to a child?
我們牽著手睡吧
Hold hands till we fall asleep?
這聽起來好像不太公平
This doesn't seem entirely fair.
好吧
Yeah, okay.
萊西
Lacey?
好  托比
Okay, Toby?
你按了嗎  再來一次
Did you hit? Hit it again.
再來
Again.
-再來  -我按了
- Hit it again. - I'm hitting it.
再按一次
Hit it again.
-你會把尸體電焦的  -托比  再來
- You're gonna fry the body. - Toby, hit it again.
再來
Again.
再電一次
Hit it again.
再來  再按一次
Again. Hit it again.
這是失敗了還是只是瓶頸
Is this just a setback or...?
我真的不知道
I'm really not sure.
你要見他嗎
Are you gonna see him?
還是想繼續視而不見
Or are you just gonna continue to ignore it?
抱歉...  我做不到
I'm sorry... I can't.
你當然做不到  你這輩子就這么窩囊
Of course you can't. Story of your fucking life.
只會逃避  把爛攤子丟給我
Just run away and leave me to deal with the mess.
你在對我的尸體做什么
What are you doing with my body?
你的尸體要在中午火化  我在做準備
Your body, is to be cremated at noon, so, I'm getting it ready.
我們還有點時間重來一遍
We do still have a little time to prep a redo.
重來  別逗了  你差點把尸體電焦
Redo? Guys, come on. You almost fried the body.
重來一遍是讓他早點火化嗎
You do this redo, you're gonna cremate him early. All right?
托比  找輛面包車  威爾說得對
Toby, rustle up a van. Will's right.
真好
It's good.
又能在實驗室見到你了  真好
Seeing you back in the labs again, it's good.
這才是你該待的地方
It's where you belong.
托比  馬上替我找具新的尸體
Toby, I want you to locate me a new corpse, immediately.
-我能問你個問題嗎  -問吧
- Hey. Can I ask you something? - Okay.
-你怎么到這兒來了  -怎么這么問
- How'd you end up here? - Why?
我回到家   發現我爸和我姐在客廳上吊了
I came home and found my dad and my sister hanging in my living room.
為了去往「來世」
To get there.
我很遺憾
I'm sorry.
沒事  他們不想帶上我
It's okay. They didn't want me to come.
你會感到被拋棄嗎
Can you imagine feeling abandoned
如果你爸沒讓你加入「全家自殺計劃」
'cause your dad left you out of the family suicide?
你怎么了
What's wrong with you?
沒  我在想事情
Nothing, I'm just... I'm processing.
你是不是活在自己的世界里出不來了
I mean, do you ever get out of your head even for one minute?
我們做個實驗  看著我
Let's do an experiment. Look at me.
看著我  說說你最先想到的念頭是什么
Look at me and tell me the first thing that comes to your mind.
我在開車
I'm driving.
好吧
Okay.
我不太了解你
I don't know you very well.
我覺得你很美  很活潑
I think you're beautiful, and alive,
你要是自殺
and if you killed yourself,
不僅是可惜  簡直是個悲劇
it wouldn't just be sad, it would be a tragedy.
少貧嘴了
Shut up.
-你抬頭還是腳  -頭
- You want the head or the feet? - Head.
好
Okay.
「艾拉  你最近忙什么」
"Hey, Isla. What are you up to?"
「沒什么  吉姆」
"Nothing much, Jim.
「只不過是把尸體拖過停車場」
I'm just... lugging a corpse through a parking lot."
為什么是「吉姆」
Why'd you go with "Jim"?
一個瞎編的人  你還吃醋
Don't be jealous of hypothetical Jim.
說真的  要是吉姆能讓你放棄自殺
Believe me, if hypothetical Jim makes you not wanna kill yourself,
我可以支持你們
I can be supportive.
就把尸體丟在這里嗎
Do we just leave it here?
你可能不信  這是我第一次還尸體
Believe it or not, it's my first time returning a corpse, so...
我只能即興發揮
I'm improvising.
你好  說來奇怪  我開車路過你們停車場
Hi, yeah, I was just driving by and this is kind of weird,
你們那似乎
but there seems to be, like,
躺著一具死尸
a dead body laying in your parking lot.
-厲害  -閉嘴  下車
- That was pretty good. - Shut up. Get out.
我在夸你做得不錯  -閉嘴
I'm saying you're doing a good job. - Stop it.
好吧
Fine.
抱歉  是  島上信號不太好
Sorry. Yeah, no, bad... Bad reception on the island.
看上去尸體像被扔在這兒的  說不好
Yeah, the body seems to be abandoned, and... I don't know.
當然了  除非
Unless, of course,
你們在玩什么扯淡的「尋寶游戲」
you guys are playing some sort of fucked-up scavenger hunt.
好的  謝謝  再見
Okay. Yes, thank you. Bye.
-怎么樣  -很順利
- How'd that go? - It went really well.
你竟然對這種事出奇得在行
Okay. You're, like, weirdly good at that.
他們過來了
Here they are.
他們也挺困惑
They're pretty confused.
你覺得他們在想什么
What do you think they're thinking?
不知道  但我覺得帕特·菲利普斯
I don't know, but I think Pat Phillips
過去幾天吃了不少苦頭
has had a really tough few days.
我們都會下地獄的
We're both going to hell.
是啊  誰知道「來世」什么樣
Yeah. Whatever the afterlife is, I guess.
太蠢了
Just stupid.
你要見他嗎
Are you gonna see him?
還是想繼續視而不見
Or are you just gonna continue to ignore it?
抱歉...  我做不到
I'm sorry... I can't.
你當然做不到  你這輩子就這么窩囊
Of course you can't. Story of your fucking life.
只會逃避  把爛攤子丟給我
Just run away and leave me to deal with the mess.
附近的醫院
如果這一世只是一場夢呢
What if this life is just a dream?
卡車借我一用
Can I borrow your truck?
我得...  去取點東西
Just for... I have to go get some stuff.
自殺不是良策  堅守此生
據我們的記錄顯示
As far as our records indicate,
醫院接受過的病人里  叫菲利普斯的有23個
we've had 23 patients with the name Phillips on file.
-你們的記錄有多準確  -很準確
- How accurate are your records? - Accurate.
我想看看名單
I would love to see that list.
我想也是
I'm sure you would.
自殺不是良策  堅守此生
搞什么
What the fuck?
你在找什么嗎
Are you looking for something?
也許你能幫我
Maybe you can help me.
-這里以前是個走廊嗎  -以前是
- Did there used to be a hallway here? - Used to.
院方改建了一下
They did a little remodeling.
還花了不少時間
Took their sweet-ass time with it, too.
抱歉  改建是多久之前的事
I'm sorry, how long ago was that remodel?
大約十年前吧
About a decade ago.
你去哪兒了
Where have you been?
發現了一件有意思的事
This is... This is interesting.
好了  謝謝你  托比
Okay, thank you, Toby.
謝謝你  孩子
Thank you, my boy.
大家好
Well, hello to you all.
一如既往  很榮幸發表講話
As always, it's a pleasure.
你們剛到這里時  你們...
When you all first got here, you...
你們都用過這臺設備
You used this, uh, piece of equipment.
填過調查問卷
The questionnaire.
你們的回答令你們得以留在此處
And your answers are what allowed you to stay here,
基本上  信任自此建起
so, basically... a trust was built.
但最近我在想
But lately, I'm beginning to wonder
我們這里是不是太安逸了
if perhaps we're getting just a little too comfortable here.
無稽之談甚囂塵上
There's a lot of loose talk going on.
不禁讓我反思
And it makes me think
也許是對你們太放松了
that we just might be losing a little focus.
萊西  能上來一下嗎
Lacey, would you join me, please?
-怎么了  -沒事  放輕松
- What's going on? - It's okay. Relax.
告訴大家  你來這里多久了
Would you like to tell us how long you've been here?
一年多
just over a year.
一年多  你是頭一批來的
Just over a year. You were one of the first.
你在此待遇如何
How have you been treated?
過得好嗎
Have you been treated well?
-我對你好嗎  -你對我很好
- Have I been good to you? - You've been wonderful.
-為什么這樣說  -對你很好
- Why are you talking to me like this? - I've been wonderful.
既然我對你很好
If I've been wonderful,
為什么你要把機器的事告訴同伴了
then why are you telling your peers about the device,
特別是...  為什么你說機器失敗了
and particularly... why are you saying it failed?
說話
Speak up.
沒關系
It's okay.
我只告訴了一個人
I just told one person.
新來的女孩受邀了  我跟人提起時
It slipped out when I had mentioned
不小心說漏了嘴
how the new girl was invited.
你是說艾拉
You mean Isla.
我邀請她  你不開心了是嗎
You were displeased when I invited her here, weren't you?
只是覺得有些在這待得更久  卻沒受到邀請
It's just that some people who have been here much longer weren't asked.
告訴大家我在哪里找到的你
Tell everyone where I found you.
托馬斯
Thomas.
沒關系的
It's okay.
你可以講
This is a safe place.
在樹林里
In the woods.
繼續
Go on.
我拿著槍
I had a gun.
你的槍對準了哪里
And where was that gun aimed?
我的胸膛
At my chest.
就在你心臟邊上
Right next to your heart.
通常想自殺的人會對準頭部
Usually, it's the head...
或是把槍管放進嘴里
or the barrel goes into the mouth.
我之前可沒見過像你這樣自殺的人
I don't know that I've ever seen it done that way before.
對不起
I'm sorry.
求你不要對我失去信任
Please don't lose faith in me.
「信任」
"Faith."
天啊  我真是瞧不起這個詞
Oh, God. I have such contempt for that word.
但凡有人依靠信任
Show me someone who relies on faith
就會有人過度信任
and I'll show you someone who's given up control
最后結局一發不可收拾
over whatever it is they believe.
抱歉  我沒什么能幫到你了  萊西
Sorry, there's nothing more I can do for you, Lacey
托馬斯  求你了
Thomas, please.
收拾好行李
Pack up your belongings.
跟大家說再見吧
Say your goodbyes.
剛才真是一出好戲啊
That was a hell of a show out there.
得了吧  威爾
Come on, Will.
你以為我不知道這里很多都是胡扯嗎
You think I don't know a lot of this is bullshit?
你給生無可戀的人提供了活下去的意義
You give meaning to people who think they have no more reason to live.
連身衣  管理系統  夸張的表演
The jumpsuit, the chain of command, the theatrics.
他們靠這些活下去  我關心他們
It gives them purpose. And I care about them.
是啊  這些話該說給萊西聽
Yeah. Someone should tell that to Lacey.
你可以繼續假裝你離開的原因是
You... You can pretend all you want that the reason you left was
你不再贊同我的成果
because you stopped approving of my work.
但別忘了  這是我倆一起的成果
Work, by the way, that we did together.
但我們都知道
But I think we both know
對你來說  一直都不是因為「重大發現」
this was never about the Discovery for you.
而是因為你的母親
It was always about your mother.
是  當然是因為我媽
Yes, of course it was about Mom for me.
你想假裝媽媽的事沒發生
Just because you wanna pretend like Mom did not happen...
不代表我也得這樣
doesn't mean that I'm going to.
-我能給你看些東西嗎  -什么
- Can I show you something? - What?
-跟我來就好  來吧  -抱歉
- Just come with me. Please. - Sorry.
等等
Wait.
-這是什么  -我也想弄明白
- What is this? - That's what I'm trying to figure out.
你之前打算一直瞞著我嗎
You were gonna keep this from me?
沒  我這不是給你看了
No, I'm... I'm showing you now.
我怕你可能還想自殺
And I was afraid of what you might do.
好吧  所以  「來世」...
All right, so, the afterlife...
這就是「來世」嗎
This is the afterlife?
這怎么可能是「來世」呢
How can it be the afterlife
我們就在上面顯示的這個停車場里
if we're sitting in the same parking lot in that recording?
那這是什么
Then what is it?
我的推論是
My theory is that
我父親發明出了某種記錄記憶的機器
my father invented something that records memory.
你聽他不停地念叨過潛意識
You've heard him go on and on about the subconscious.
我知道你希望是其它結果
I understand that you wanted this to be something different.
但事實勝于雄辯  這是帕特·菲利普斯的記憶
The proof is overwhelming that that's a Pat Phillips memory.
「事實勝于雄辯」還不夠  要拿出確鑿證據
Proof shouldn't be overwhelming. It should be definitive.
我們到底要去哪里啊
Where the fuck are we going?
如果視頻中的事真實發生過
If what we're seeing on that video happened in real life,
我要查出何時發生的
I'm gonna find out exactly when.
這家醫院自開辦以來
Since this hospital opened,
一共收過23個叫菲利普斯的患者
there have been 23 patients named Phillips.
但根據他的貨車型號
But based on the model of his truck,
我可以排除2000年之前入院的菲利普斯
I can eliminate any Phillips from before the year 2000.
但就算是2000年之后  也還是有好多人吧
Yeah, but even after 2000, doesn't that leave a lot of names?
那間病房不存在了
That hospital room doesn't exist anymore,
所以我們可以交叉比對過去十年
so, we can also cross off any Phillips
入過院的菲利普斯
from the past decade.
那就只有這一個了
That leaves us with one.
「康納·菲利普斯」
"Connor Phillips"?
就是他
That's him.
這是帕特·菲利普斯的父親
That's Pat Phillips' dad.
他十三年前死在這里
He died here 13 years ago.
這么說  機器只是錄下記憶嗎
So, it does just record a memory?
今天的事真是太操蛋了  對吧
It's pretty fucked up what happened today, huh?
萊西的事
With Lacey?
她說錯話了
She spoke out of turn.
她知道規矩
And she knew the rules.
她有份參與訂下這些規矩
She basically helped write them.
這里就咱倆說話呢
It's just you and me talking.
你不是真信這些吧
You don't believe that.
別跟我說我該信什么  威爾
Stop telling me what I believe, Will.
證明「來世」的存在  毀了爸的一生
Proving the existence of an afterlife destroyed Dad's own life.
這才是我相信的
That's what I believe.
還毀了別人的人生
Yeah... everybody else's, too.
爸沒打算
Dad has no intention...
將機器記錄的一切公之于眾
of showing anything the machine records with the outside world.
所以萊西告訴別人時  他才失控了
That's why he lost it when Lacey told people.
如果他沒打算將這臺機器的作用公之于眾
If he has no intention of showing what it does to anybody,
那還研究什么  還有什么意義
why is he doing it, huh? What's the point?
「他還研究什么」
"Why is he doing it?"
想想看吧
Let's see.
他會跟你說說  死去的上百萬人
he'll tell you about the millions of people who died,
他會告訴你  完成這項研究是為了紀念那些人
and he'll tell you about finishing his work to honor them.
我昨天聽過了
I heard that yesterday.
而我都聽了兩年了
I've been hearing that for the past two years now.
我就微笑  點頭  贊同...
And I just... smile and nod and agree...
像個低智商的兒子  但我心里跟明鏡一樣
like the idiot son, but I do understand things.
我知道媽死了...
I know Mom died...
不是死了  是自殺
Not died. She killed herself.
她自殺了
She killed herself.
你看看...
And when you look...
爸畢生的研究
at what Dad spent his life working on,
再看看媽自殺的方式
and when you look at the way Mom killed herself,
她是如何自殺的
how she did it...
爸內疚的同時
how would Dad not feel a little anger
怎么可能會不憤怒呢
on top of his guilt?
爸必須得弄明白
Dad does need... to know.
他需要知道她去到「來世」了
He needs to know that she made it somewhere.
他反應過激了而已
He overreacted, that's all.
他會醒悟過來  萊西明天就會回來
He'll come to his senses, and, Lacey will be back by tomorrow.
爸總是能醒悟過來
Dad always comes to his senses.
那不是記憶  威爾
It's not a memory, Will.
什么
What?
他左手臂上的同一位置  紋身圖案不同
On his left arm in that exact spot, there was a different tattoo.
-這怎么可能  -不知道  但我在實驗室見過
- How is that possible? - I don't know, but in the lab, I saw it.
不是燈塔  他手臂上的圖案是波浪
It wasn't a lighthouse. It was waves on his arm.
-你確定嗎  -我確定
- Are you sure? - Yes. I'm sure.
威爾  這不是記憶  而是其它解釋
Will. It's not a memory. This is something else.
如果不是記憶  那是什么呢
If it's not a memory, then what is it?
我們見到的一切都不存在了
Everything we've seen doesn't exist anymore.
那間病房不在了  帕特·菲利普斯顯然也不在了
I mean, the hospital room's gone, Pat Phillips, obviously gone.
我們得找出視頻中還存在于現實的事物
We need to find something in this video that still exists.
那個女人  有一個...
The... the woman. There's a...
她
Her.
康納·菲利普斯的死亡證明書上有家里地址
We have Connor Phillips' address on his death certificate.
不如我們明天過去瞧瞧
So, I say that we go down there tomorrow...
看看有沒有人能幫我們找到她
and we see if somebody can help us track her down.
威爾  我們怎么回到這里了
Will, why are we back here?
我不知道我們去那間房子會查到什么...
I don't know what's waiting for us at that house, and I...
你記得我和你說過  我小時候發生的意外嗎
Do you remember I told you about my accident when I was a kid?
記得  你騙你媽說看到一些東西
Yeah, when you lied to your mom about what you saw.
我沒騙她
I didn't lie.
我就是在這里看到的...
This is where I saw whatever...
不管我看到的景象是什么  就在這個海灘上
Whatever it is that I saw. This is the beach.
我小時候經常來這里  就像...
I used to come here when I was a kid, like...
這里有種魔力吸引我
I was drawn to it.
或者說這里讓我感覺好受點
Or it made me feel better.
總之
Anyway...
所以那天我看見你走進水里...
when I saw you walking into the water the other day, that's...
所以我才出現了
That's why I was here.
怎么了
What?
我之前有個兒子
I had a son...
他當時五歲
and he was five years old.
我睡著了
And I fell asleep...
就一小會兒
just for a second.
我醒來時  他不見了
And when I woke up, he was gone.
我一開始感覺  我不該與你相識...
At first I thought I wasn't supposed to meet you...
不該有什么感覺
or feel anything.
但也許我想錯了
But maybe I was wrong.
你好  這里是菲利普斯的家嗎
Hi. Is this the Phillips residence?
康納  你認識康納·菲利普斯嗎
Connor... Did you know Connor Phillips?
帕特·菲利普斯呢  你會說英語嗎
Pat Phillips? Can you speak English?
好吧
Okay.
顯然她不是視頻中的那個女人
Okay, well, that's clearly not the woman from the video.
也許他們搬走了吧
Maybe they moved or something.
要不看看他們有沒有遷新地址
Should we see if they have the new address?
不知道  不知道
I don't know. I don't know.
有什么事嗎
Can I help you?
我已經很多年沒見過我哥了
I haven't seen my brother in years.
比起我  更失落的是她吧
I'd call it more of a loss for her than for me.
阿茲海默癥「老年癡呆」Alzheimer's.
父親死后  她的病情就開始惡化
She deteriorated after Dad died.
-康納嗎  -你認識我父親嗎
- Connor? - You knew my father, too?
其實是聽帕特提過
You know, actually, Pat mentioned him.
他說他在父親死前  去看望過他
That he went to see him before he died.
總之  父親死后
Well, anyway, Dad died and...
母親的身體狀況就急轉直下
Mom, she started going downhill real fast after that.
這幢房子現歸我和我丈夫所有
My husband and I, we own the house now.
你們會給帕特安排什么追悼會嗎
Is there gonna be a service or anything, um, for Pat?
我不知道
I wouldn't know.
抱歉  恕我直言
I'm sorry, if you don't mind me saying,
但感覺你對你哥的死并不難過
you just ,you don't seem that upset about your brother's death.
是這樣
Look...
看來你們好像挺喜歡這個人
it seems as though you liked him.
你們看到了他的某些特質
You found something in him...
但是我很抱歉
so, I'm sorry.
對于我們來說  他就是個人渣
But to the rest of us... he was a piece of shit
留他妹妹一人照顧罹患癌癥的父親
who left his sister with a cancer-ridden father
還有神志不清的母親
and a mother who lost every marble she ever had.
抱歉  那么你最后一次見帕特
I'm sorry. So... is the last time that you saw Pat
就是他去醫院看你們父親
when he went to visit your Dad in the hospital?
我不知道他跟你們都瞎說了些什么
I don't know what bullshit he hauled your way,
但他從沒去醫院看過父親
but he never visited my father in the hospital.
如果他說去了  那就是說謊
If he told you that, it's a lie.
他打過電話說要來看他  但從未露面
He called and said he was gonna visit him, but he never showed up.
這么問也許有點怪  帕特有紋身嗎
This is gonna sound really strange, but did Pat have a tattoo?
他告訴你的嗎
He told you about that?
他十八歲的時候  我們一起紋了一對波浪
When he turned 18, we got matching waves.
我們當時關系很好
We were really close then.
看來機器記錄那段的不是記憶
So, the machine doesn't record a memory.
你爸的結論沒錯
It wasn't a bad theory.
人們會一直繼續自殺
People are just gonna keep killing themselves.
你遲早都得原諒你父親  威爾
You know, sooner or later, you're gonna have to forgive your dad, Will.
我一直在思考  事物的本身和其意義
I've been thinking a lot about the difference between...
究竟有什么不同
what something is and what something means.
我不知道這段記錄到底是什么
And I don't know what any of this is...
但我知道  如果這背后真有某種意義
but I do think if there's a meaning to any of it,
應該是無論生活如何艱辛
it has something to do with not pressing the reset button,
都不該選擇自殺重活
even if things get really rough.
人們兜兜轉轉
We're a bunch of people running around,
一次又一次重復過去的錯誤
making the same mistakes over and over.
為什么會覺得換了個地方  就會有所不同
And I don't know why we think it'll be different somewhere else...
除非這一世  我們已經學到應有的教訓
unless we learn what we're supposed to learn while we're here.
你兒子叫什么名字
What was your son's name?
奧利弗
Oliver.
我在做夢
I was dreaming.
他掉進海里的時候  我在做夢
When he was in the water, I was dreaming.
什么夢
What about?
說不清
I don't know.
我不記得了
I can't remember.
就是你知道自己在做夢
It was one of those times where you know for sure you're dreaming,
但是不知道...
but you just don't...
夢境的內容
don't know what about.
我要是知道就好了
I wish I knew.
如果很難受  你可以不用一個人承擔
You don't have to do this alone anymore if you don't want to.
威爾
Will!
媽的  威爾
Fuck! Fuck, Will!
快起來  爸出事了  你干什么呢
Get up. It's Dad. What the fuck are you doing?
爸怎么了
What about Dad?
-爸出事了  趕緊起來  -好  我來了
- It's dad. Get the fuck up. - Okay. All right. I'm coming.
我不懂  所以我沒辦法阻止
I didn't know, so, I couldn't stop it.
冷靜點  告訴我到底怎么了
Slow down and tell me exactly what happened.
他把自己連上了機器
He hooked himself up to the device.
他想證明機器沒問題
He wanted to prove that it works.
-爸連上機器了嗎  -對
- Dad's hooked up right now? - Yes.
我們得告訴他  機器有用
We need to tell him that it works.
什么
What?
什么有用
What works?
-你們搞什么  -他要求的
- What are you doing? - He demanded.
-為什么不弄醒他  -太遲了
- Why aren't you bringing him back? - He's too far along.
我們已經知道機器能記錄一些東西
We already know that it records something.
庫珀
Cooper...
機器有用
it works, okay?
爸
Dad?
你該停下了
Time to pull yourself away.
回歸現實  回家吧
Come back to reality. Come home.
-是媽嗎  -是她
- Is that Mom? - It's Mom.
我的研究就是現實
What I'm doing is reality.
我得完成  這很重要  你明白嗎
I need to finish. It's important. Do you understand?
-他們的結婚紀念日  -對
- Their anniversary. - Yeah.
我要上樓了
I'm going upstairs.
別鬧情緒好嗎
Now, don't be dramatic.
我馬上就完成  我們可以一起用晚餐
I'll be done soon. And we can have dinner.
親愛的  等一下
Honey, wait.
也許工作可以先放一放
Maybe work can wait.
一起用晚餐怎么樣
So, what do you say we have some dinner?
她沒去泡澡
She's not taking the bath.
-當時不是這樣的  -我知道
- That's not what happened. - I know.
我們可以讓他醒過來了
We can bring him back.
庫珀  等一下  我們得看看發生了什么
Cooper, just... wait. We have to see what happens.
必須現在動手  否則就太遲了
We've got to do it now, or it'll be too late.
威爾  快點
Will, come on.
托比  抱歉  庫珀  趕快
Toby, I'm sorry. Cooper, now!
爸  爸  聽我說
Dad? Dad, listen to me.
爸  拜托  聽聽我的聲音
Dad, please. Listen to my voice.
他是不是要腦...
Is he gonna be brain...?
我不知道  我不知道
I don't know. I don't know.
庫珀  再來一次
Cooper, hit it again!
爸
Dad?
怎么了
What happened?
我知道我看到她了
I knew I saw her.
就像一個記不起來的夢
Like a dream that you can't remember.
我不知道這是怎么回事  爸
I can't figure out what this is, Dad.
我之前從沒離開過書房
I never left my study.
從沒阻止她上樓
Never stopped her on the stairs.
-然后她就去泡澡了  -我知道
- And she drew a bath. - I know.
帕特·菲利普斯的記錄里
And in the Pat Phillips recording,
他胳膊上有個不一樣的紋身
he has a different tattoo on his arm.
我常說「來世」就是「另一個次元世界」
I always said the afterlife was a different plane of existence.
但是...
But...
萬一是這個世界的另一個次元呢
what if it's a different plane... of this existence?
現實世界的另一個版本
Alternate realities?
不  就是我們的世界  不過略有差別
No, our reality... with differences and variations.
走下卡車  看望垂死的病人
Stepping out of a truck... to visit a dying parent.
存在隨機性  就像那個不同的紋身
Random, like different tattoos.
阻止別人上樓結束自己的生命
Stopping someone from going upstairs to end their life.
當我們死了
When we die,
萬一我們是去另一個版本的今生呢
what if we travel to an alternate version of our own life?
第二次機會
A second chance?
那我們就不必面對自己最深的悔恨了
Then we wouldn't... just have to accept our biggest regret.
我們可以在「來世」改變這一切
In the afterlife, we could change it.
這不就顯然說明自殺...
At the risk of stating the super fucking obvious...
如果你們是對的  消息傳了出去...
If you are right and word of this got out--
我們得銷毀這臺機器
We have to destroy the machine.
托馬斯
Thomas.
大家都想知道怎么回事
Everyone wants to know what's going on.
歡迎各位  很高興你們都能過來
Welcome, everybody. Nice to have you all here.
我今天叫你們過來
I asked you to gather here today
因為我覺得我們該坦誠相待
because I thought that we should be honest.
坦誠于自己
Honest with ourselves,
坦誠于彼此
honest with each other.
你能再次見到你媽媽了
You got to see your mom again.
我視你們為家人...
I see you as family...
相信你們也視我為家人
and I think you see me in the same way.
作為家人...
And as family...
我覺得有時候我們太過執著于
I think sometimes we get so absorbed with...
我們自己的事
what we're doing individually,
我們沿著自己的軌道一路向前
we go off on our own track and so forth,
卻忘記了家人有多么重要
we lose the fact that how important family is.
萊西
Lacey?
Lacey.
萊西  沒關系的  把槍放下
Lacey, it's okay. Put the... put the gun down.
萊西  是我錯了  你不必這么做
Lacey, I was wrong. You do not need to do this.
我沒有殺她
I didn't kill her.
我只是送她去到了別處
I just relocated her.
艾拉
Isla?
艾拉  沒事的
Isla. Oh, it's okay.
艾拉  爸  天吶
Isla? Dad! God.
爸  拜托  來幫幫我
Dad, please! I need your help!
誰去叫救援來
Somebody go get help.
我只是想要回自己的位置
I just wanted my spot back.
艾拉  爸爸  求你救救她
Isla. Dad, please help her.
別說話  保持呼吸
Don't talk. Just breathe.
我不再想死了
I don't wanna die anymore.
你不會有事的  千萬別睡過去
You're okay. I just need you to stay with me.
艾拉
Isla?
警方問
They were asking, the cops,
艾拉的聯系人是誰
who to contact for Isla.
她的親屬
Next-of-kin deal.
-我會讓庫珀去查一下  -好
- I'll have Cooper look into it. - Okay.
現在別去問他太多問題了
I don't wanna overwhelm him with questions right now, okay?
你說得對
That's probably a good idea.
我該進去看看他吧
Maybe I should go in and check on him...
不不不  別去
No, no, no. Don't.
他需要休息
He needs rest.
他需要點時間消化
He needs to process, okay?
晚飯后  你可以去看他
You can check on him after dinner.
然后我們今晚就把這機器拆了
And then we'll finish breaking down the machine tonight.
但是...
But...
我們還沒能...
we haven't come close...
弄清楚這一切及其背后的意義
to figuring this all out yet, or what it all means.
如果那真是我們今生的另一個版本
Like, if it really is another version of our own life,
那么在那個「今生」中死去會怎樣呢
then what happens when we die again?
托比
Toby.
-托比  -怎么了
- Toby. - What?
我們必須得收手一陣子了
We've got to let it go for a while.
我們必須得這么做
We've just got to.
全拆了
Completely dismantled.
所有痕跡都要銷毀
All traces need to be gone.
托馬斯  我懂了
Thomas, I hear you.
威廉
William?
讓我們進來  別這么做
Let us in, don't do this.
威廉
William.
他在來這里的船上
He's on the ferry headed here?
-不是同一個「這里」  -什么
- Not the same here. - What?
我不明白
I don't understand.
如果他沒死  我們為什么能看到這些畫面
How are we watching this right now if he's not dead?
托馬斯·哈勃公布「重大發現」之后
...since Thomas Harber's first and only
首次接受了獨家專訪時
post-Discovery interview
有人突然在節目中自殺
ended suddenly with an on-air suicide.
自此之后  全世界的自殺人數暴增到...
Since then, the worldwide suicide toll has sky--
我正在看呢
I was watching that.
艾拉
Isla?
-艾拉  -現在是淡季
- Isla? - It's off-season.
你去這個荒涼的小島干什么
Why are you going to this dreary island?
艾拉
Isla?
-我要阻止你被槍擊中  艾拉  -坐下
- I have to stop your shooting, Isla. - Sit down.
我要你現在就和我一起走
I need you to come with me right now.
坐下  威爾  這只是記憶而已
Sit down, Will. This is just your memory.
我是你意識中的一部分  坐下
I'm a part of you. Sit down.
我們怎么又回到這條船上了
What are we doing back on this ferry?
這到底是怎么回事
What the fuck is going on?
只有「這一世」  你才阻止了我自殺
You were never able to stop me from killing myself until this life.
「這一世」  你說什...
"This life"? What do you...?
「這一世」是什么意思
What do you mean, "this life"?
你總是從回到渡輪上
You always start back on the ferry.
現實和幻想相互獨立
Reality and fantasy are mutually exclusive.
兩者無法共存
They don't exist in the same space.
看來我們到了
Well, it looks like we're here.
我改主意了
You know what? I changed my mind.
我不知道我之前怎么想的
I don't know what I was thinking.
第一次  你沒下船
The first time, you never got off the ferry.
第二天  你看到新聞
Then the next day you read that
一個叫艾拉的女人投海自盡了
a woman named Isla had drowned herself.
你繼續過著自己的生活
You went on and lived your life,
但本來能幫上忙的想法一直揮之不去
but the thought that you could've done something never left.
一直縈繞著你
It was always there.
有一天  就像其他人一樣
And then one day, just like everybody else...
我死了
I died.
然后你就回到這里
And then you came back here.
我困在這個循環里多久了
How long have I been stuck living in this loop?
我們在渡輪上遇見多少次了
How many times have we met on this ferry?
你一死就會回到這里
Your death brings you back here.
你一遍又一遍地回到這個原點
You keep coming back over and over again and again.
我一點都不記得
I don't remember any of it.
我不記得其他「幾世」
I don't remember these other lives.
沒人能直接想起來
Nobody can remember them directly.
但有時  記憶能通過某些方式留在腦海里
But sometimes certain memories do have a way of sticking out.
我覺得你好眼熟  我覺得你好眼熟
You look so familiar to me. You look so familiar to me.
你很走運啊  我出門一般不帶這玩意
It's your lucky day. I don't normally carry these around.
不管我看到的景象是什么  就在這個海灘上
This is where I saw whatever... This is the beach.
你怎么知道自己會住這一間
How'd you know this is where you were gonna be staying?
我們這群人兜兜轉轉
We're a bunch of people running around
一次又一次重復過去的錯誤
making the same mistakes over and over.
為什么會覺得換了個地方  就會有所不同
And I don't know why we think it'll be different somewhere else...
我應該改變什么
What am I supposed to change?
你已經改變了
You already changed it.
你不斷地回來  直到救了我
You kept coming back until you saved me.
我沒救你  你死了
I didn't save you, you died.
救人不止有一種方法  威爾
There's more than one way to save somebody, Will.
庫珀  準備好  我們得讓他蘇醒
Cooper, ready on our end. We need to bring him back.
我怎么能聽到我爸的聲音  他又不在這里
How can I hear my dad? He's in a different place.
兩個次元的同一處地方
Two separate parts in the same place.
好了  爸  除顫器充好電了
Okay, Dad, defibrillator's charged.
不不不  我還沒準備好回去
No, no, no. I'm not ready to go back yet.
我要多跟你待一會兒
I need more time with you.
托比  等等  先別這樣做
Toby, please wait! Not yet!
他的生命體征很危險
His vitals are concerning me.
要是現在把他拉回來  可能會失去他
If we pull him now, we might lose him.
艾拉  艾拉  求你了
Isla. Isla, please.
我還沒準備好離開你
I'm not ready to leave you.
-我怎么了  -你快死了
- What's happening to me? - You're about to die.
他心臟停跳了  托馬斯
His heart's stopped, Thomas.
器官逐漸衰竭
Organs are shutting down.
他們想把你救回去
They're trying to bring you back.
沒關系
That's okay.
我要是死了  就會直接回到你身邊吧
Because If I die, I'll just come back here to you, right?
不  這次不是
No, not this time.
你不用再回來了
You don't have to come back anymore.
你幫去了我該去的地方
You helped me get to where I needed to be
現在你該去往「別處」了
and now you'll go someplace else.
等我去了「別處」  我還能記得你嗎
When I get there, will I be able to remember you?
希望能
I hope so.
爸  各項器官都衰歇了
Dad, everything is shutting down.
他的大腦活動幾乎停止了
His brain's showing barely any activity.
你現在就走  到此為止了
You're leaving now. This is it.
不救回我兒子  我不會離開這間屋子
I'm not leaving this room until we revive my son.
等我去了「別處」  我會記得你
When I get there... I'm going to remember you.
我們得把他拉回來
We've gotta pull him out right now.
一  二  三
One... two... three.
你還好嗎
Look. You okay?
-嗯  -過來
- Yeah. - Come here.
我來幫你一把  過來  過來
Let me help you. Come here, come here.
我抓到你了
I got you.
你還好嗎
You okay?
-天啊  -把桶給我
- Holy cow. - Give me that pail.
-你摔得不輕啊  -是啊
- You went down pretty good, huh? - Yeah.
你還好嗎  我抱著你呢
Yep. You okay? I got you.
你的爸爸媽媽呢
Where's your mom and dad?
奧利弗
Oliver!
沒事的  他沒事  只是...
It's okay. He's all right. He just...
-好了  -我告訴過你  你不能...
- Okay. - I told you, you can't--
你不能那樣亂跑  明白嗎  我說過的
You can't just run off on me like that, okay? I've told you.
他只是...  他沒事的
He was... he was just... He's all right.
他在水里有點掙扎
He was struggling a little bit in the water.
我想確保讓他回到你身邊
I wanted to make sure he got back to you.
-你沒事吧  -嗯
- Are you okay? - Yeah.
-謝謝  -沒事
- Thank you. - Yeah.
他是個好孩子
He's a good kid.
-你還好  -謝謝
- You're okay. - Thanks.
你可別再那么干了  你嚇到我了  好嗎
You can't do that. You scared me. Okay?
你能下來自己走嗎
Can you walk a little bit?